Hi.
We're going to talk a little bit about how to accessorize using your bracelets.
The first few examples that we have are this one here.
This one's a little bit fancier, and typically you would think about pairing it up with something, something more glamorous, that you'd be going out for an evening out on the town.
I, on the other hand, like the mix things up a little bit, pairing up fancy, stylish things with a casual outfit.
So for me, this would be something that I might want to have some fun with.
Second bracelet option that we have is this one here.
This is an example of a charm bracelet.
And one that I can see going well with a sparkly ring.
Finally, we have the single pennant bracelet that actually would work well with a necklace.
You can find one that matches it, switch it up a little bit, play around with it, but always stick to silver with the earrings and necklace, if that's what the color of your bracelet is.
Also if you're wearing a bracelet, it's a good idea to make sure that one piece of jewelry is your stand out piece.
Everything else needs to be a little bit more subtle so that the eye doesn't have conflicting interest.
Finally this last watch that we have is actually made for a man.
Men can wear bracelets as well as women.
This one kind of resembles a watch band without the watch face on it, and can be worn in a variety of ways with a variety of outfits.
Join us in the next segment and we're going to talk about anklets.